http://www.squeegees.net/privacy

ETTORE RUBBERS
ETTORE RUBBERS (SINGLES)
ETTORE RUBBERS (12)
ETTORE RUBBERS (144)
MOERMAN LIQUIDATOR RUBBERS
MOERMAN RUBBERS (SINGLES)
MOERMAN RUBBERS (10)
PULEX RUBBERS
PULEX RUBBERS (SINGLES)
PULEX RUBBERS (12)
PULEX RUBBERS (144)
SORBO RUBBERS
SORBO RUBBERS (SINGLES)
SORBO RUBBERS (12)
SORBO RUBBERS (144)
UNGER RUBBERS
UNGER RUBBERS (SINGLES)
UNGER RUBBERS (12)
UNGER RUBBERS (144)
Privacy Notice
Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services.
What Information Do We Collect?
When you visit our Web site you may provide us with Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.
Email Information.
If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses.
Web Site Use Information
Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies?”) and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site. We, our advertisers and ad serving companies may also use small pieces of code called “web beacons” or “clear gifs” to determine which advertisements and promotions users have seen and how users responded to them.
How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?
Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering and expanding our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. You may notify us at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers by emailing us at info@squeegees.net
What Are Cookies?
A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.
How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?
As you shop on our Web site, the site uses its’ cookies to differentiate you from other shoppers so your shopping cart is only available to you. In some cases, we also use cookies to prevent you from seeing unnecessary advertisements or requiring you to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with our Web server’s log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our Web site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback in order to constantly improve our Web site and better serve our customers. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not generally store any personal information that you provided to us in your cookies.
Notice of New Services and Changes
Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. As our customer, you will be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by sending us an email request at info@squeegees.net
How Do We Secure Information Transmissions?
Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. Some of the information you may enter on our Web site may be transmitted securely via Secure Sockets Layer SSL, 128 bit encryption services, which are enabled by VeriSign, Inc. Pages utilizing this technology will have URLs that start with HTTPS instead of HTTP. Please contact info@squeegees.net if you have any questions or concerns.
How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?
You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by emailing info@squeegees.net .
Certain Disclosures
We may disclosure your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law or comply with legal process served on us or Affiliated Parties; (b) protect and defend our rights and property, the Site, the users of the Site, and/or our Affiliated Parties; (c) act under circumstances to protect the safety of users of the Site, us, or third parties.
What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?
We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site.
Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Web site to another Web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your’ browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including Web sites which have a link on our Web site, is subject to that Web site’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.
Your Consent
By using our Web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our Web site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it.
Categories
APPARELBELTS, HOLSTERS & ACCESSORIESGLOVES, HELMET, MASKS, BOOTIESBUCKETSCLEANINGCLOTHSDUSTING - UNGER HIGH ACCESSGUTTERS & OUTDOOR CLEANINGSTINGRAY INDOOR POLE CLEANINGCLEANING CHEMICALSGLASS, LUBRICANTS & SEALERSDEGREASERS,RESTORATION, STAINGUTTERS,SIDING & SCREEN CLEANERSSOLAR CLEANINGAWNING CLEANERS & PROTECTANTSLOUVERS,BLINDS, SCREEN CLEANINGRESTROOM & WET FLOOR MAINTENANCECOVID19GLASS SCRATCH REPAIRHIGH-RISEBOATSWAIN'S CHAIRSCARABINERSDESCENDERSHARNESSESHELMETRIGGING EQUIPMENTROPE GRABS & LANYARDSROPES & ROPE CARESUCTION CUPSSIGNS & CAUTION TAPELADDERSSECTIONAL LADDERSLADDER ACCESSORIESPOLESETTORE POLES & ACCESSORIESGARELICK POLES & ACCESSORIESMOERMAN POLES & ACCESSORIESUNGER OPTILOC POLES/ACCESSORIESUNGER ADDANARM POLES/ACCESSORIESSCRAPERS & BLADESHAND HELD POCKET SCRAPERSETTORE SCRAPERSUNGER SCRAPERSSORBO SCRAPERTRIUMPH SCRAPERSSLEEVES, T-BARS & BRUSHESETTORE SCRUBBERSMOERMAN SCRUBBERSPULEX SCRUBBERSSORBO SCRUBBERSUNGER SCRUBBERSSCRUBBER/SQUEEGEE COMBOSBRUSHESSPONGESSQUEEGEES & RUBBERSRUBBERSETTORE RUBBERSETTORE RUBBERS (SINGLES)ETTORE RUBBERS (12)ETTORE RUBBERS (144)MOERMAN LIQUIDATOR RUBBERSMOERMAN RUBBERS (SINGLES)MOERMAN RUBBERS (10)PULEX RUBBERSPULEX RUBBERS (SINGLES)PULEX RUBBERS (12)PULEX RUBBERS (144)SORBO RUBBERSSORBO RUBBERS (SINGLES)SORBO RUBBERS (12)SORBO RUBBERS (144)UNGER RUBBERSUNGER RUBBERS (SINGLES)UNGER RUBBERS (12)UNGER RUBBERS (144)ETTORE SQUEEGEESETTORE BRASS SQUEEGEESETTORE STEEL SQUEEGEESETTORE SUPER CHANNEL SQUEEGEESMOERMAN SQUEEGEESPULEX SQUEEGEESSORBO SQUEEGEESSORBO COBRA SQUEEGEESSORBO QUICK SILVER SQUEEGEESSTECCONE SQUEEGEESUNGER SQUEEGEESUNGER NINJA SQUEEGEESUNGER STEEL SQUEEGEESWAGTAIL SQUEEGEESSQUEEGEE/SCRUBBER COMBOSTHE LEDGERVIDEOS & TRAINING BOOKSWATER PURIFIERS2 STAGE DI PURIFIERIPC EAGLE HYDROCART & HYDROTUBEHYDROCART PURIFIERHYDROTUBE PURIFIERRHG/TUCKERTUCKER DI PURIFIEREZ PURE PURIFIERETTORE 4 STAGE PURIFIERSH2PRO 3 STAGE PURIFIERSTUCKER PURIFIERFILL N GO TRUCK MOUNTED PURIFIERGUTTER POLE & VACUUMUNGER HYDROPOWERWATERFED POLESGARDINER WATERFED POLESTELESCOPIC POLESBRUSHES & ACCESSORIESGOOSENECKS & POLE FITTINGSREPLACEMENT GARDINER SECTIONSMAGNUM WATERFED PARTSUNGER NLITE WATERFED PARTSWATERFED KITGUTTER (EAVESTROUGHS) CLEANINGINDOOR WATERFED POLESTUCKER WATERFED POLESWATERFED CONVERSION KITHOSES, ACCESSORIES & PUMPSHOSES, CONNECTORS & REELTDS METER & WATER KEYHOSE VALVES, FLOW CONTROLSBACKPACK & PUMPS
Currencies
US Dollar
Canadian Dollars
INFORMATION
Shipping and Returns
Privacy Notice
Terms and Conditions
Leasing
Newsletter
Subscribe to our newsletter and receive the latest offers, discounts and updates. During checkout simply check the box that says "Subscribe to newsletter"
© Copyright © Squeegees.net. | Owned by Canada Cleaning Supplies Ltd.
Website Development by WSG
